Guide to the Chloe Faith Dzubilo Papers 1976-2011 MSS.397
Fales Library and Special Collections
Chloe Faith Dzubilo Papers
1976-2011
1995-2011
Fales Library and Special Collections
Dzubilo, Chloe
MSS.397
11 Linear Feet in 7 boxes and 4 record cartons
Chloe Faith Dzubilo was an artist and AIDS and transgender activist. The Chloe Faith Dzubilo Papers comprise art, photographs, writing, annotated books, various annotated paper materials, journals, correspondence, articles, flyers, invitations, posters, brochures, objects, and audiovisual materials. The papers document Dzubilo's life as an artist, and a transgender woman living with HIV/AIDS while advocating for the rights and representation of people with HIV/AIDS and the transgender community.
Biographical Note
Chloe Faith Dzubilo (1960-2011) was an artist and AIDS and transgender activist.
Dzubilo moved to New York City from Connecticut in 1982, working at Studio 54 before becoming the advertising director at the East Village Eye. She wrote for and performed with the Blacklips Performance Cult at the Pyramid club and edited the group's zine, Leif Sux, and was in the band Transisters. In 1987 she was diagnosed with HIV when Bobby Bradley, her partner of nine years and founder of the Pyramid Club, died of AIDS. Following her diagnosis, Dzubilo advocated for civil rights, adequate health care and dignity for people living with HIV/AIDS, transgendered people, and drug users.
Dzubilo studied art at the Parsons School of Design and received an associate degree in Gender Studies from the City University of New York City College in 1999. She served on New York City's LGBT Community Center's Gender Identity Project transgender HIV prevention team, conducting prevention outreach; spoke at conferences and in video Public Service Announcements, and gave workshops for health care and mental health providers. Dzubilo was involved with the political action group the Transsexual Menace, and went on to direct one of the first federally funded HIV prevention programs for transgender sex workers in 1997.
In 2001, Dzubilo founded the Equi-Aid Project, a Manhattan-based program that specifically helps children who are infected with or affected by HIV/AIDS, as well as other at-risk youth. In 2003, Dzubilo was appointed to the HIV and Human Service Planning Council of New York, an advisory body composed of people living with HIV/AIDS, service providers, and government representatives, charged with ensuring that "people living with HIV have access to appropriate, quality services across the continuum of care, resulting in the best possible health and quality of life."
Dzubilo died on February 18, 2011.
Source: Visual Aids.
Scope and Content
The Chloe Faith Dzubilo Papers comprise artworks, photographs, writing, annotated books, various annotated paper materials, journals, correspondence, articles, flyers, invitations, posters, brochures, objects, and aidovisual material. These materials document Dzubilo's life as an artist, and as a transgender woman living with HIV/AIDS advocating for the rights and representation of people with HIV/AIDS and the transgender community.
Series I: Artwork contains art made by Dzubilo in various mediums on paper and cloth.
Series II: Photographs contains both personal and professional photos taken of Dzubilo, her friends, and family.
Series III: Writing contains poetry and stories written by Dzubilo as well as personal correspondence.
Series IV: Journals & Annotated Books contains published books and guides that Dzubilo wrote in along with journals, notebooks, and planners.
Series V: Press & Ephemera contains articles from publications featuring Dzubilo and flyers, brochures, posters, and invitations for various events and organizations.
Series VI: Objects contains items collected by Dzubilo, including a jar of her medications.
Series VII: Audio Recordings contains commercially released audio, live recordings, and master tapes.
Series VIII: Data Storage contains DVD-R and CD-R discs with files related to Dzubilo's art.
Series IX: 2016 Accretion: Equestrian Materials contains items related to Dzubilo's equestrian pursuits and includes riding boots, a helmet, and chaps.
Series X: Books contains contains published books donated with the collection.
Arrangement
The Chloe Faith Dzubilo Papers are divided into ten series:
Series I: Artwork
Series II: Photographs
Series III: Writing
Series IV: Journals & Annotated Books
Series V: Press & Ephemera
Series VI: Objects
Series VII: Media
Series VIII: Data Storage
Series IX: 2016 Accretion: Equestrian Materials
Series X: Books
Provenance
The collection was transferred from Visual Aids to Fales in 2014. In April 2016, an additional donation of equestrian-related objects was donated; the accession number associated with this collection is 2016.017.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Separated Materials
Books from this collection that were not annotated by Dzubilo were removed and will be catalogued through BobCat.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Born-digital and audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
AIDS activists -- New York (State) -- New York; AIDS (Disease) and art -- United States.; Diaries; Artists -- New York (State) -- New York.; Drug addiction.; Transgender artists; LGBT activism.; Transgender people -- Civil rights.; Printed ephemera.; Poetry.; Safe sex in AIDS prevention -- United States.; Punk rock music.; Visual AIDS (Organization); De Long, T; Transsexual Menace; Equi-Aid Project; Transisters
- Series I: Artwork, 2004-2010; 275620
  Scope and Content
  This series contains artwork created by Dzubilo using various mediums on paper and cloth. Majority of the work relates to life or advocacy for people with HIV/AIDS and transgender people. Some art also is either created with or about Dzubilo's partner T De Long.
  Arrangement
  Series I is arranged alphabetically by title of the artwork. If there is no title, the folders are arranged chronologically.
  - Artwork on Paper, 2008; 275650 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2008-2009; 275651 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2009; 275652 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Artwork on Paper [Isabel Celeste/Mama D], 2008; 275653 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Artwork on Paper and Photo [Michael Bloomberg], 2004-2008; 275654 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Birds of a Feather Flock Together, 2009; 275655 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cause and (Side) Effects, March/April 2010; 275656 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - [Eyes and Feather Collage], undated; 275657 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - [Medication List Artwork], undated; 275658 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - [Photocopy Art], [2010]; 275659 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Untitled (1st Transgender March), 2008; 275660 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Untitled (Correct Term), 2008; 275661 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Untitled (Flower Lady), undated; 275662 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Untitled (I Love Native American Culture), 2008; 275663 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Untitled (The Tranny Chasers), 2008; 275664 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Series II: Photographs, 1983-2004; 275621
  This series contains both professional and personal photographs of Dzubilo, her family, and friends. Alice O'Malley and Katrina del Mar frequently photographed Dzubilo, and their work can be found throughout the series. Dzubilo's noted can also be found on the back of most photographs.
  Series II is arranged in original order the photographs were found in the collection.
  - Professional and Personal Photographs, 1983-2004; 275648 (Binder A)
- Series III: Writing, 1988-2010; 275622
  This series contains both poetry and short stories written by Dzubilo as well as her personal correspondence. Binder #1 and the folders of its contents contains poetry, stories, notebooks, correspondence, and Equi-Aid material written by Dzubilo. Cover letters and recommendation letters can also be found in this series.
  Series III is arranged alphabetically.
  - #1 Fragile Strips of Poems as Mobile, undated; 275665 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - #2 Poem Mobile, undated; 275666 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - #3 Poem Mobile [Envelope Only], undated; 275667 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Binder #1 [Empty], undated; 275668 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Binder #1 Contents [1 of 3], 1988-2010; 275669 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Binder #1 Contents [2 of 3], 1988-2010; 275670 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Binder #1 Contents [3 of 3], 1988-2010; 275671 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Chloe Poems, 2009; 275672 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Contact Information, undated; 275673 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Copyright Office Correspondence, February 14, 1997; 275674 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Dedication, undated; 275675 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - [Edited Cover Letter], undated; 275676 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Emails with Writings Sent to Herself, January 2010; 275677 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Estate Planning Correspondence, August 22, 2008; 275678 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Greeting Cards from Family, undated; 275679 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Letter from Kembra, April 28; 275680 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Letter of Recommendation from Executive Director Richard D. Burns at the LGBT Community Center, December 10, 2001; 275681 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Medical Correspondence, September 5, 2007; 275682 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Mobile Poems (copies), 2010; 275683 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Note by Vita Kurland Given by Alice O'Malley, undated; 275684 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Paper Magazine Correspondence, March 15, 2000; 275685 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Poems, 2009; 275686 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Thank You Card from Margaret Ha, undated; 275687 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - [Untitled Poem - Partial], 2009; 275688 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - [Untitled Poem], undated; 275689 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - [Untitled Story and Poetry], May 29, 1988; 275690 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Visual Aids Loan Agreement, August 8, 2012; 275691 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - [Writing], undated; 275692 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Series IV: Journals & Annotated Books, 1976-2011; 275623
  This series contains journals, planners, and notebooks as well as published books, guides, papers, and envelopes that Dzubilo wrote notes in and annotated.
  Series IV is arranged alphabetically.
  - 2011 Planner, 275693 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 2011 Planner, 275694 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Alcoholics Anonymous, 1976; 275695 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Alcoholics Anonymous, January 1, 2009; 275696 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Angry Women in Rock Volume One [No Front Cover], 1996; 275697 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - [Annotated Envelopes], undated; 275698 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - [Annotated Folder], undated; 275699 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - The Da Vinci Method by Garret La Porto, 2008; 275700 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Godspeed by Lynn Breedlove, 2002; 275701 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - How Al-Anon Works for Families & Friends of Alcoholics, 1995; 275702 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - It Works: How and Why, 1993; 275703 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - [Journal], undated; 275704 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Making Movies by Sidney Lumet, 1995; 275705 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Narcotics Anonymous Step Working Guides, 1998; 275706 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - One Day at a Time in Al-Anon, 1973; 275707 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Paths to Recovery, 1997; 275708 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - [Partial Notebook], 2010; 275709 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - [Printed Pictures with Notes], 1977; undated; 275710 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - [Quote Inspirational Book with No Cover], undated; 275711 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Steps We Took by Joe McQ, 1990; 275712 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Twelve Steps and Twelve Traditions, 2005; 275713 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Series V: Press & Ephemera, 1984-2011; 275624
  This series contains articles from publications about Dzubilo regarding her art, performances, activism, and personal life. Material related to her Equi-Aid Project can also be found in this series. Flyers, posters, brochures, programs, and invitations to events are also included. Paperwork from Dzubilo's name change and In Memory of Card after her passing is also located in this series.
  Series V is arranged alphabetically.
  - 13th Annual Postcards from the Edge: A Benefit for Visual Aids Program, 2011; 275715 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bellwater by Tanyth Berkeley Review from Time Out New York, April 5-11, 2007; 275716 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Calling All Girls: Transgenders and HIV, 1997; 275717 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Capricious #12, 2011; 275718 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - [Chloe Envelope], undated; 275719 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chloe and Tara De Long Interview in Heterosexualisms, undated; 275720 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Chloe and Tara Jo De Long Marriage Blurb from Next Magazine, undated; 275721 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - [Chloe and Tara - Page from Unknown Magazine], undated; 275722 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Equi-Aid Project 1st Annual Benefit Invitation, May 20; 275723 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Equi-Aid Project Brochure, undated; 275725 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Funeral Programs, 2000-2006; 275726 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - HIV Plus Magazine #1, September 1998; 275727 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - In Memory of Chloe Faith Dzubilo Card, 2011; 275728 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - The Marker of Hate from New York Blade, July 23, 2008; 275729 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Mixed Messages Show Program, June 2-July 3, 2011; 275731 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Mixed Messages Visual Aids Show Articles, 2011; 275732 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Name Change Paperwork, 1995; 275733 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - [New York City AA Meeting Schedule], undated; 275734 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Outsider Art Fair Invitation, 2011; 275736 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - POZ Magazine 10th Anniversary Cover, May 2004; 275737 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Press, 1984-2008; 275738 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Return to Freedom: American Wild Horse Sanctuary Newsletter, [2009]; 275739 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Tanyth Berkeley "Love Parade" Invitation [from Tanyth], 2005; 275740 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Trans Day of Remembrance Program, November 20, 2009; 275741 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Transeuphoria Invitation, January-February; 275742 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Transisters Articles, 1995-1996; 275743 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Transisters Gig Fyler, November 21; 275744 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Transisters "The Goddesses of Pink Rock" Album Insert, 1995; 275745 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Transisters Press, 1995-1996; 275746 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - "Visiting Desire" Time Out New York Summary/Review, undated; 275747 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Windows by Duane Dzubilo, undated; 275748 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Series VI: Objects, 275625
  This series contains various items collected by Dzubilo including a jar of her medications, annotated cookie box, Keith Harring bag, Empire State College diploma cover, wallet and cards, framed photograph, and Narcotics Anonymous keychains. A riding crop and dress part of Series VI are located in Box 5.
  Series VI is arranged at the box level.
  - Box of Objects, undated; 275877 (Box 6)
- Series VII: Audio Recordings, 275626
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audio materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  This series contains cassette tapes ands CDs. Annotated envelopes that the audio recordings were found in are also included in this series.
  Series VII is arranged alphabetically by title.
  - AIDS Be Gone: Volume One, undated; ID: 397.0001; 275921 (Box 7, Media ID: 397.0001)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Original Format: CD
    Currently unavailable
  - Annotated Envelopes for Audio Recordings, undated; 276244 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Transisters: 1st Show Live at The Cooler, June 5, 1995; ID: 397.0002; 275919 (Box 7, Media ID: 397.0002)
    Original Format: 1/4" Audiocasette
  - Transisters - Goddesses of Pink Rock, undated; ID: 397.0003; 275920 (Box 7, Media ID: 397.0003)
  - Transisters Latest Rehersal: "Fetish", "Boy/Girl," "Horses," "Vagina," "Lotsa," Transie Chaser", undated; ID: 397.0004; 275916 (Box 7, Media ID: 397.0004)
  - Transisters Masters & Recordings: "Horses to Heroin," "Carolina Vagina," "Transie Chaser," "Lotsa Glamour," "Kaposis Koverstik", undated; ID: 397.0005; 275918 (Box 7, Media ID: 397.0005)
    Original Format: Digital Audio Tape
  - Transisters Recordings: "Horses," "Carolina," "Lotsa," "Kaposis", undated; ID: 397.0006; 275917 (Box 7, Media ID: 397.0006)
- Series VIII: Data Storage, 275634
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  This series contains DVD-R and CD-R discs with digital files of Dzubilo's artwork. Annotated envelopes that the data storage materials were found in are also included in this series.
  Series VIII is arranged alphabetically by the title orignally written on the disc.
  - 24 Scans - TIFF, JPEG, undated; 275929 (Box 7, Disk 397.3.0001)
  - Annotated Envelopes for Data Storage, 2007; undated; 276245 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Art from the Prince George, 2010; 275932 (Box 7, Disk 397.3.0002)
  - Chloe Dzubilo, undated; 275930 (Box 7, Disk 397.3.0003)
  - DVD Demo, undated; 275928 (Box 7, Disk 397.3.0004)
  - Drawings, August 2008; 275927 (Box 7, Disk 397.3.0005)
  - Early Drawings 2008 Transhealth, 275931 (Box 7, Disk 397.3.0006)
  - LGBTQ On Rye, undated; 275933 (Box 7, Disk ID: 397.3.0007)
  - Low Res Drawings, undated; 275924 (Box 7, Disk ID: 397.3.0008)
  - Low-Res Drawings, undated; 275925 (Box 7, Disk ID: 397.3.0009)
  - Mount Sinai Radiology Associates: MRI KNGG, September 5, 2007; 275934 (Box 7, Disk ID: 397.3.0010)
  - Slide Show Drawing, undated; 275926 (Box 7, Disk ID: 397.3.0011)
  - Visual Aids Drawings O'Malley, 2010; 275923 (Box 7, Disk ID: 397.3.0012)
- Series IX: 2016 Accretion: Equestrian Materials, 277398
  This series consists of objects related to Dzublio's equestrian pursuits. Items include riding boots, pants, chaps, a riding helmet, a boot jack, and a boot hook. A book, The Spirit and the Flesh: Sexual Diversity in American Indian Culture by Walter L. Williams that was housed with this materials upon arrival, is also present.
  - Chaps, circa 1976-2011; 278473 (Box 8)
  - Riding Pants, circa 1976-2011; 278474 (Box 8)
  - Boot Hook, circa 1976-2011; 278475 (Box 8)
  - Boot Jack, circa 1976-2011; 278476 (Box 8)
  - Riding Helmet and Case, circa 1976-2011; 278477 (Box 9)
  - Riding Boots, circa 1976-2011; 278478 (Box 10)
  - Duffel Bag, circa 1976-2011; 278479 (Box 10)
- Series X: Books, 1972-2008; 1 Linear Feet 1 record carton.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains several volumes donated with the collection.
  - Al-Anon's Twelve Steps & Twelve Traditions, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Allen, Mariette Pathy. The Gender Frontier, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Cameron, Julia. Inspirations, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Darling, Candy. My Face for the World to See, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Field, Genevieve. Nerve/The New Nude, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Goldin, Nan. The Beautiful Smile, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Lynch, David. Catching the Big Fish, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Mao Mag Vol. 1, Issue 8, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - O'Malley, Alice. Community of Elsewheres, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Parkett no. 57, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Pfahler, Kembra. The Voluptuous Horror of Karen Black, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Storm, Hyemeyohsts. Seven Arrows, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- OVERSIZE Series I: Artwork, 2004-2010; 275628
  - Art on Balenciaga and Prada Bags, 2010; 275636 (Folder 1 Left)
  - Artwork on Canvas Cloth, 2010; undated; 275771 (Folder 1)
  - Artwork on Canvas Cloth, undated; 275772 (Folder 2)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2007-2010; undated; 275637 (Folder 2 Left)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2008; 275777 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2008; 275778 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2008; 275779 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2008; undated; 275780 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2008-2011; undated; 275781 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2009; 275782 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2009; 275783 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2009; 275784 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2009-2010; 275785 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2009; undated; 275786 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2009-2010; undated; 275638 (Folder 3 Left)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2010; 275787 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2010; 275639 (Folder 4 Left)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2010-2011; 275788 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2010-2011; 275789 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2010; undated; 275790 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2010; undated; 275792 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2011; 275791 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Artwork on Paper, 2011; 275793 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Artwork on Paper, undated; 275794 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Artwork on Red Cloth, undated; 275773 (Folder 3)
  - Blacklips Performance Cult Opens "Vagina" Poster, May 16; 275640 (Folder 5 Left)
  - Calendar Art, February-October 2004; 275641 (Folder 6 Left)
  - "Can I Have Your Attention...", undated; 275795 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Earn the Seat, 2008; 275796 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fertility Beauty, 2009; 275797 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - [List of Affairs], undated; 275798 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - "Long Term" Survivor Hospital Gown by T De Long & Chloe and Folder, undated; 275775 (Box 5)
  - "Long Term" Survivor T Shirt by T De Long & Chloe, undated; 275776 (Box 5)
  - "Our Worldz, Native"; Untitled (I'm Never the Top); Untitled (Medicated w/ 5 mgs Methodone), 2009; 275799 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - "Tara", 2009; 275800 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - "Tara Tso", undated; 275801 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - "teej tjjdo", 2008; 275802 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - "There is a Transmutation" Marker on Canvas List, undated; 275803 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Transeuphoria Poster, Jan 20-February 13; 275645 (Folder 14 Right)
  - Untitled (1st Drag), 2008; 275804 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Untitled (3 Gramercy Park), 2008; 275805 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Untitled (Ahead of the Times), 2008; 275806 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Untitled (Aging Lifestyle), 2009; 275807 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Untitled (Are You In Labor), 2008; 275808 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Untitled (As Long As), 2010; 275809 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Untitled (Badly Wired Leader), 2008; 275810 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Untitled (Brand Her Kinky), 2008; 275811 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Untitled (Bridgehampton View of 1994), 2010; 275812 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Untitled (Bud No Wiser), 2008; 275813 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Untitled (Buddy Bill), 2008; 275834 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Untitled (Coach), 2008; 275835 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Untitled (A Cop Once Smacked Me), 2008; 275836 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Untitled (Crimes of Humanity), 2008; 275837 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Untitled (Emergency Care), 2008; 275838 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Untitled (Figure Study I, II, III), 2009; 275839 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Untitled (Green Drawing), 2008; 275840 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Untitled (Green Green), 2009; 275642 (Folder 7 Left)
  - Untitled (Green Ink Drawing I, II, III), 2009; 275841 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Untitled (He Came With Much Drama), 2008; 275842 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Untitled (He'll Risk Anything), 2008; 275843 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Untitled (HIV Housing), 2008; 275844 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Untitled (Hospital), 2008; 275845 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Untitled (How Many Priests), 2008; 275846 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Untitled (I Ask Myself), 2010; 275643 (Folder 12 Right)
  - Untitled (Kickbacks), 2008; 275847 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Untitled (Kickboxing for T-Girls), 2008; 275848 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Untitled (Later at the County Fair), undated; 275849 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Untitled (Lyrics I wrote in '95), 2008; 275850 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Untitled (Medical Records), 2008; 275851 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Untitled (The Most Un-PC Questions), 2008; 275852 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Untitled (The Only Blood), 2009; 275644 (Folder 13 Right)
  - Untitled (Paxyl Smith Kline), 2008; 275853 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Untitled (Polysexual), undated; 275854 (Box 4, Folder 20)